

hatsot.github.io

Scan to check my work

CONTACT

SKILLS

6946023620

| hatsot.github.io

COMMUNICATION

MANAGERIAL

BUSINESS

BAD JOKES

DESIGN

hatsot89@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/sothat

Sotiris Chatoupis

Senior Product Designer

ABOUT ME

Hi, I'm Sot! I studied electrical engineering but later on, found my self falling in love with design and especially product design. I am interested in all stages of Design Thinking, while I love working close with all other fields such as marketing, business, dev teams and pms. Currently, I'm working as a senior product designer at dSphere.io and have 4 years experience leading small design teams

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sep 2022 - Present

dSphere.io

Senior Product Designer

web3 SaaS platform with a robust suite of products built to scale and support any web3 project from ideation to results

Jun 2020 - Present

Lead Designer, Co-founder

Beautly

wappier

Enables beauty services at home with a marketplace app that connects beauticians with customers

Mar 2017 - Sep 2022

Senior Product Designer

Wappier provides through its platform the tools to maximize user life time value in mobile apps & games

Ad-Hoc projects while at wappier

Jul 2020 - Sep 2021

Lead Designer

PWC-NN

As part of PWC team, I redesigned the UI/UX of myNN portal for NN Hellas, both for web and mobile app

Jan 2019 - Jun 2020

Lead Designer

Taponit deals

Redesign of the taponit mobile deals web site, to make it more functional and improve the experience of the user

HOBBIES Jan 2017 - Dec 2021

TENNIS • PHOTOGRAPHY • READING GUITAR • BASKET • COMEDY • EATING



UI/UX Designer

WIZZO

More than 5 million players use Wizzo to upload and stream videos, win prizes and experience new games

EDUCATION

Electrical and Computer Engineering at National Technical University of Athens

SIDE HUSTLE 🕠 🥃

May 2021 - Present Co-host

The Greek Tennis Podcast

News and views about ATP & WTA tour

